<Document>
  Welcome to [bold][color=green]GreenShift[/bold][/color] (patent pending). These rules are fairly light, but failing to follow them will result in admin action.

  ## Rule 0 - Admin Rulings are Final
  Admins are a trusted position, and as such are trusted to make decisions for the health of the community and game.

  If you have a problem with an admin using this rule, bring it up in a [bold]staff complaint ticket on the Discord[/bold] for Senior Admin and Maintainer review.

  ## Rule 1 - Respect Others / Don't Be A Dick
  Everyone's here to have fun, and roleplay is a requirement.
  You don't have to be a kind person in-character, but being respectful out-of-character is mandatory.

  Bigotry of any kind is [bold][color=red]not[/bold][/color] tolerated, and will result in a permanent ban without exception.

  If you can't act at minimum like an adult, you may be removed from the game or community.

  If you're generally unwelcoming, unhelpful, or otherwise consistently toxic, you may be removed from the game or community.

  Don't use hacks or cheats or modified clients.

  Antag rolling is not allowed. If you join the game, stick to the role you get.

  ## Rule 2 - Roleplay is a Requirement
  Although one of the core goals of the server is to reduce the need for admin intervention & restriction of player agency through rules, you are still expected to roleplay.

  Meaningful conflicts are a core part of all parts of the game, and it should generally be enjoyable for all parties, even if one loses without a chance of fighting back.
  Be proportional with your responses - someone insulting you might start a fight, but it doesn't mean you should jump straight to killing them.

  ## Rule 3 - No Erotic Roleplay (ERP)
  Don't be creepy or overly-suggestive.

  Adult-leaning jokes are fine but they should remain in-character.

  Erotic Roleplay of any kind will immediately lead to a [bold]permanent[/bold] ban.

  ## Rule 4 - Play Your Character
  There's a lot of lee-way given for character names - that being said, don't use a real-life reference or an obviously stupid name. Admins reserve the right to ask you to change your name if they feel it is too on-the-nose for any reason.

  Don't use Out-Of-Character information gained during a round (such as a voicechat with a friend or a stream of the game).

  Generally aim to follow the objectives and instruction given to you by the game - including the job that you selected. You are expressly allowed to use all information at your disposal to make decisions.

  Silicons must follow all of their laws to the best of their ability. This is non-negotiable.
</Document>
